

JHONNY IRIARTE

Software Engineer

Yes, I'm Jhonny Iriarte Condori, a 29 year old full-stack developer with experience in React, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Node.js and Linux server administration. I am characterized by my dynamism, joy and perseverance. My passion for learning and facing technical challenges drives me constantly. I am excited to bring my energy and skills to collaborative teams and take advantage of new opportunities.

Education

• Software Engineer

Academio Full-Stack Web Development and Computer Science Course

2022-2023

Financial Engineering

Diploma in Banking and Financial Risks

2014-2021

 Telecommunications Technician

2008-2011

Software management.

- Css
- Linux
- Javascript
 Node.js
- Html
- React
- Postgres SQL
- Taildwind
- Githup

Contacto



+591 74320607



iriarte.condori.jhonny25@gmail.com



jhonny-iriarte-condori.netlify.app



Bolivia, Cochabamba, Tiquipaya

Experience

Academio

Sep 2022 - ago 2023

I have a strong background in developing projects using React.js, JavaScript, Node.js, CSS, and PostgreSQL. My expertise includes creating dynamic and responsive web applications, leveraging efficient database management, and ensuring seamless user experiences.

Nerds OnSite

Dic 2019 - ago 2023

Deployment and Management of Digital Services on Linux Servers

II worked as an independent contractor in the deployment, implementation, and management of the Zabbix business model as a monitoring system for pfSense devices, ensuring its efficiency and adaptation to the client's needs

SALCEDO PRO

Dic 2018 - ago 2019

Social media management

As an independent contractor, I played a pivotal role in content creation and management on social media platforms. I also contributed to the strategic framework, offering ideas that propelled its development and expansion.

Digital NetWork.srl

Dic 2011 - Ago 2013

Operational Technician in Structured Cabling.

I specialize in structured wiring, cabinet assembly, and network connectivity, ensuring efficient and reliable telecommunications solutions.

Languages

• Quechua (Nativo) • Ingles (Intermedio) • Español (Avanzado)

Skills

- Organization
- · Meeting deadlines
- Communication
- · Critical thinking
- Teamwork